Took the micro swagger, shined a self-made crown Planned to drain the system, tear corruption down But all we got were hashtags, anime parade Cryptic jokes and punchlines, nothing really changed Rode the hype with tweets like kings of clown town Toted revolution came back, run down
Fucked you dark, fixed the mess, saved the day, clout a trillion in waste, you said hooray.
Watch your rocket crashed on launch, so cliche, nine billion pennies, that's all you saved.
Hey you, so not special anyway.
Hey you, just a meme of yesterday K-Market for dough, wild on the stage Selling moon tickets but just pocket change Big suit in black, I the circus, the act Golden key from Trump, hollow as a fax Camera flashes, thick confetti, paper crown
You're a punchline painted as a breakthrough clown But you dodged, fixed the mess, saved the day Cut a trillion in waste, you said hooray But your market crashed on launch, simply shade Nine billion pennies, that's all you saved Hey you, so not special anyway Hey you, just a meme of yesterchange Big suit and black eye, the circus, the act
Golden key from Trump, hollow as the fax Camera flashes, Bitcoin, Benny, paper crown You're a punchline painted as a breakthrough clown Top deal, fix the mess, save the day Cut a trillion in ways to say hooray But your rocket crashed on launch, so cliche
Nine billion pennies, that's all you splayed Hey you, so not special anyway Hey you, just a meme of yesterday